原创翻译  双语字幕
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.ZiMuZu.tv
翻译：somehacker 杏仁斯嘉丽 木浅 x6324
翻译：小英的小号 小蛮腰
时间轴：狮市长Ans 羊副市长路帕斯 尼克浪浪
时间轴：闪电Jessie 豹警官Meng 牛局长姜姜
校对：somehacker
后期：吉吉     总监：somehacker
疯狂动物城
恐惧  背叛和嗜血
Fear, treachery, blood lust.
数万年前支配着我们的世界
Thousands of years ago these were the forces that ruled our world
那时食草动物惧怕食肉动物
A world where prey were scared of predators.
而食肉动物无法遏制的本能
And predators had an uncontrollable...
让他们捕猎  残杀  还有
biological urge to maim, and maul, and...
流血  血  血
Blood! Blood! Blood!
和死亡
And.. Death!
那时世界分成两部分
Back then, the world was divided in two.
凶残的食肉动物  和温顺的食草动物
Vicious predator, or meek prey.
凶残的食肉动物
温顺的食草动物
但我们也随着时间进化
But over time, we evolved,
将这原始野蛮的生活方式抛在身后
and moved beyond or primitive savage ways.
现在食肉和食草动物和谐共处
Now predator and prey live in harmony.
每只哺乳动物的未来都有了无限可能
And every young mammal has multitudinous opportunities.
我不用再缩在羊群里了
Yeah, I don't have to cower in a a herd anymore.
英文的黑羊Black Sheep等于中文的害群之马
我可以做宇航员
Instead, I can be an astronaut.
我不用再孤单地追捕狩猎了
I don't have to be a lonely hunter anymore.
我可以追捕逃税的人
Today I can hunt for tax exemptions.
我要做精算师
I'm gonna be an actuary.
我可以让世界更美好  我要做
And I can make the world a better place. I am going to be...
警察
A police officer!
兔子警察  简直蠢透了
Bunny cop? That is the most stupidest thing I ever heard!
眼界狭窄的当然觉得不可能
It may seem impossible to small minds.
说的就是你  吉迪恩·格雷
I'm looking at you, Gideon Grey.
但是211英里外就是伟大的动物城
But, just 211 miles away, stands the great city of Zootopia.
我们双方的祖先签订和平契约
Where our ancestors first joined together in peace.
胡萝卜日才艺秀
正式宣布  谁都能成就无限可能
And declared that anyone can be anything!
谢谢大家  晚安
Thank you and good night.
朱迪  你想没想过
Judy, you ever wonder how
你妈妈和我为什么这么幸福吗
your mom and me got to be so darn happy?
没有
Nope.
我们放弃了梦想  安定了下来  对吗邦妮
Well, we gave up on our dreams, and we settled. Right, Bon?
是啊  斯图  我们可安定了
Oh, yes. That's right, Stu. We settled hard.
这就是知足常乐  朱迪
You see, that's the beauty of complacency, Jude.
不尝试新的事物  就绝不会失败
If you don't try anything new, you'll never fail.
我挺喜欢尝试的
I like trying, actually.
亲爱的  你爸爸是说
What your father means, hon,
成为警官对你来说非常难
is that it's gonna be difficult, impossible even...
甚至是不可能的
for you to become a police officer.
是啊  还从没有兔子做过警察
Right. There's never been a bunny cop.
-没有  -兔子不做警察
- No. - Bunnies don't do that.
-绝不会  -绝不
- Never. - Never.
那我就是第一个了
Well... Then I guess I'll have to be the first one.
因为我要让世界更美好
Because I am gonna make the world a better place!
或者  这样
Or, heck, you know.
想让世界更美好吗
You wanna talk about making the world a better place,
做个种胡萝卜的农民最好了
no better way to do it than becoming a carrot farmer.
是啊  你爸爸和我  还有你275个兄弟姐妹
Yes! Your dad, me, your 275 brothers and sisters.
我们就是在改变世界
We're changing the world.
-一根胡萝卜一根胡萝卜地拯救  -可不是嘛
- One carrot at a time. - Amen to that.
种胡萝卜是光荣的职业
Carrot farming is a noble profession.
只要把种子
Just pulling their seeds out
撒进土里
And one with the soil...
懂吗  有梦想是好事
You get it, honey? I mean, it's great to have dreams.
只要别陷进去就好
Yeah, just as long as you don't believe in them too much.
她去哪了
Where the heck'd she go?
把票给我
Give me your tickets right now,
不然揍扁你温顺的小屁股
or I'm gonna kick your meek little sheep butt.
住手  吉迪恩
Cut it out, Gideon!
咩咩  你要哭吗
Baah, baah! What are you gonna do, cry?
-听她的  快住手  -戏服不错  小废物
- You heard her. Cut it out. - Nice costume, loser.
你是活在什么地方
What crazy world are you living in
觉得兔子能当警察吗
where you think a bunny could be a cop?
乖乖把票还给他们
Kindly return my friend's tickets.
有种来拿  但是小心点
Come and get them. But watch out.
因为我是狐狸
Cause I'm a fox,
你在那蠢货舞台剧上野说了
and like you said in your dumb little stage play,
以前食肉动物吃食草动物
us predators used to eat prey.
杀手本能还在我们的DANA里
And that killer instinct's still in our DANA.
那个  应该是DNA
Uh, I'm pretty much sure it's pronounced DNA.
我知道  不用你告诉我  崔维斯
Don't tell me what I know, Travis.
我不怕你  吉迪恩
You don't scare me, Gideon.
现在怕了吗
Scared now?
看那鼻子抽的  她怕了呢
Look at her nose twitch, she is scared.
哭吧  小兔兔  哭吧
Cry, little baby bunny! Cry...
你就是不肯放弃是吧
Oh, you don't know when to quit, do you?
你给我记住这一刻
I want you to remember this moment
免得你再不安分
the next time you think you will ever be...
忘了自己就是只种胡萝卜的蠢兔子
anything more than just a stupid carrot-farming dumb bunny.
-好重啊  -你没事吧  朱迪
- That looks bad. - Are you okay, Judy?
我没事  给你
Yeah, yeah, I'm okay. Here you go.
-你把票拿回来了  -你真棒  朱迪
- Wow, you got our tickets! - You're awesome, Judy.
吉迪恩·格雷真是胡说八道
Yeah, that Gideon Grey doesn't know what he's talking about!
有件事他是说对了
Well, he was right about one thing.
我就是不肯放弃
I don't know when to quit.
动物城警官学校
听好了  菜鸟们
Listen up, cadets.
动物城境内有12个独特的生态系统
Zootopia has 12 unique ecosystems within its city limits.
15年后
比如冰原镇  撒哈拉广场  热带雨林区
Tundratown, Sahara Square, Rainforest District, to name a few.
正式上岗前
You're gonna have to
每个区域都要非常熟悉
master all of them before you hit the streets.
不然呢  就死了
Or guess what? You'll be dead!
炽热沙尘暴
Scorching sandstorm.
死了  兔宝宝
You're dead, bunny bumpkin.
一千英尺攀高
One thousand foot fall.
死了  胡萝卜头
You're dead, carrot face.
冰墙攀岩
Frigid ice wall.
死了  小山妞
You're dead, farm girl.
大块头罪犯  死了
Enormous criminal. You're dead.
死了  死了  死了
Dead. Dead. Dead.
脏马桶  死了  小毛球
Filthy toilet. You're dead, fluff butt.
退学回家吧  毛兔兔
Just quit and go home, fuzzy bunny.
-从没有兔子当过警察  -从没有
There's never been a bunny cop. - Never.
-从没有  -种胡萝卜的蠢兔子
- Never. - Just a stupid carrot-farming dumb bunny.
作为动物城的市长
As mayor of Zootopia,
我很荣幸地宣布  哺乳动物选拔行动的
I am proud to announce that my mammal inclusion initiative,
第一批警校学员已经毕业了
has produced its first police academy graduate.
本届毕业生代表  警校第一位兔子警官
Valedictorian of her class, ZPD's very first rabbit officer...
朱迪·霍普斯
Judy Hopps.
头羊市长助理  她的警徽
Assistant Mayor Bellwether, her badge.
-对了  -谢谢
- Oh, yes, yes! - Thank you.
朱迪  我很荣幸地
Judy, it is my great privilege
将你分配到动物城的中心
to officially assign you to the heart of Zootopia...
一区  市中心
Precinct One. City Center.
恭喜你  霍普斯警官
Congratulations, Officer Hopps.
我不会让你失望的
I won't let you down.
这是我从小的梦想
This has been my dream since I was a kid.
这是属于我们小动物的骄傲
You know, it's a real proud day for us little guys.
头羊  快点让开
Bellwether, make room, will you? Come on.
好了  霍普斯警官  笑一个
Okay, Officer Hopps. Let's see those teeth!
霍普斯警官  看这里
Officer Hopps, look here.
-我们真为你骄傲  朱迪  -也有点担心
- We're real proud of you, Judy. - Yeah, and scared too.
-是啊  -又骄傲又担心
- Yes. - Really, it's kind of a proud-scared combo.
动物城啊  那么远  那么大
I mean, Zootopia. So far away, such a big city.
爸妈  我这辈子都在为这一刻努力
Guys, I've been working for this my whole life.
我们知道  我们是替你高兴  也有点害怕
We know. And we're just a little excited for you, but terrified.
除了恐惧  没什么好害怕的
The only thing we have to fear is fear itself.
还有熊  熊也要怕
And also bears. We have bears to fear, too.
-更不用说狮子和狼了  -狼
- Say nothing on lions, and wolves. - Wolves?
-黄鼠狼  -你还和黄鼠狼玩过牌
- Weasels. - You played cribbage with a weasel once?
是啊  他那作弊真是没底线
Yeah, he cheats like there's no tomorrow.
说真的  食肉动物都一样
You know what? Pretty much all predators.
-动物城全都是  -斯图
- And Zootopia is full of them. - Oh, Stu.
狐狸是最差劲的
And foxes are the worst.
你爸爸说的有点道理
Yeah, actually, your father does have a point there.
这是天生的  还记得吉迪恩·格雷吗
It's in their biology. Remember what happened with Gideon Grey?
我才九岁  他是个混蛋  刚好也是只狐狸
When I was nine. Gideon Grey was a jerk who happens to be a fox.
我认识的兔子里也有不少混蛋呢
I know plenty of bunnies who are jerks.
是啊  可不是  可是以防万一
Sure, yeah, we all do, absolutely. But just in case,
我们给你弄了个爱心包
we made you a little care package to take with you.
-放了点点心  -这是震狐器
- I put some snacks in there. - This is fox deterrent.
-拿着挺放心的  -驱狐喷雾
- Yeah, it's safe to have that. - This is fox repellant.
又震慑又驱赶  够了
The deterrent and the repellant, that's all she needs.
-看看这个  -天哪
- Check this out! - Oh, for goodness sake!
不用带电狐器吧  斯图
She has no need for a fox taser, Stu.
得了吧  电狐器总能用得上
Oh, come on. When is there not a need for a fox taser?
好了  好吧  我带着这个  好让你们消停
Well, okay, look, I will take this... To make you stop talking.
太棒了  大家都开心
Terrific! Everyone wins!
进站列车  终点动物城
Arriving, Zootopia Express.
好了  得走了  再见
Okay, gotta go. Bye!
我爱你们
I love you, guys.
爱你
Love you, too.
天哪  要哭鼻子了
Oh, cripes, here come the waterworks.
斯图  振作点
Oh, Stu. Pull it together.
大家再见
Bye everybody!
再见  朱迪  我爱你
Bye Judy, I love you! Bye!
再见
Bye!
正驶离兔窝镇
人口
夏奇羚
动物城
我是夏奇羚  欢迎来到动物城
I'm Gazelle. Welcome to Zootopia.
欢迎来到穿山甲公寓
And welcome to the Grand Pangolin Arms.
魅力四射的豪华公寓
Luxury apartments with charm.
每月一次免费除虱  钥匙别丢了
Complementary delousing once a month. Don't lose your key!
谢谢
Thank you.
-你们好  我是朱迪  新邻居  -我们声音可大了
- Oh, hi! I'm Judy, your new neighbour! - Yeah? Well, we're loud.
也不会道歉的
Don't expect us to apologize for it.
油油的墙
Greasy walls.
晃晃的床
Rickety bed.
疯癫的邻居
Crazy neighbors.
我喜欢
I love it!
别这样  他先露的牙
Come on! He bared his teeth first!
你好
Excuse me!
在下面
Down here!
-你好  -我的天哪
- Hi. - O... M... Goodness!
还真找了只兔子啊
They really did hire a bunny.
天哪  说实话
Ho-whop! I gotta tell you,
你比我想的还要可爱
you're even cuter than I thought you'd be.
你可能不知道
Ooh, ah, you probably didn't know,
兔子可以互相说可爱
but a bunny can call another bunny "Cute",
但是换了其他动物  就有点...
but when other animals do it, that's a little...
真抱歉  我  本杰明·爪豪斯
I am so sorry! Me, Benjamin Clawhauser.
大家都以为我
The guy everyone thinks is
只是爱吃甜甜圈的软萌警察  还给你套刻板印象
just a flabby donut-loving cop, stereotyping you.
没事的
No, it's okay.
你那里有个  那个
You've actually got... there's a...
-什么  -脖子里  领子上面
- A what? - In your neck. The fold.
-那个  -你在这啊  小坏蛋
- The... this... - Oh, there you went, you little dickens!
我得去点名了  哪边...
Hehehe, I should get to roll call, so which way do I...
-候补区在那边左侧  -谢谢
- Oh, bull pen's over there to the left. - Great. Thank you!
这小兔子会被生吞活剥的
That poor little bunny's gonna get eaten alive.
我是霍普斯警官  准备好让世界更美好了吗
Officer Hopps. You ready to make the world a better place?
全体都有
Attention!
好了  好了  都坐下
All right. All right. Everybody sit.
我这里有三件事
I've got three items on the docket.
首先来说屋子里的大象
First, we need to acknowledge the elephant in the room.
显而易见的事
弗朗辛  生日快乐
Francine. Happy birthday.
第二件事
Number two.
有些新人我得介绍一下
There are some new recruits with us I should introduce,
我就不介绍了  因为  我不在乎
but I'm not going to because... I don't care.
最后  有14起哺乳动物失踪案
Finally, we have 14 missing mammal cases.
全是食肉动物  从大北极熊到小水獭
All predators. From a giant polar bear to a teensy little otter.
市政厅天天追在我屁股后面
And City Hall is right up my tail to find them.
这是头等大事  任务分配
This is priority number one. Assignments.
灰熊利  牙迈尔  德尔加多警官
Officers Grizzoli, Fangmeyer, Delgato.
你们负责热带雨林区的失踪案
Your team take missing mammals from the Rainforest District.
麦克角  犀威兹  狼法德警官
Officers McHorn, Rhinowitz, Wolfard.
你们负责撒哈拉广场区
Your teams take Sahara Square.
河马金斯  吼洛夫  象克鼻警官  冰原镇
Officers Higgins, Snarlov, Trunkaby. Tundratown.
最后  第一只兔子  霍普斯警官
And finally, our first bunny, Officer Hopps.
交通协管  解散
Parking duty. Dismissed.
交通协管
Parking duty?
局长  牛局长
Chief? Chief Bogo?
长官  你说有14起哺乳动物失踪案
Sir. You said there were fourteen missing mammal cases.
-所以呢  -我可以负责一起
- So? - So I can handle one.
您可能忘了  我毕业时是班里第一名
You probably forgot but, I was top of my class at the academy.
没忘  就是不在乎
Didn't forget. Just don't care.
长官  我可不是只吉祥物
Sir, I'm not just some token bunny.
那一天开100张停车罚单应该没问题
Well then, writing a hundred tickets a day should be easy.
100张  我才不开100张呢
100 tickets. I'm not gonna write 100 tickets.
我要开200张  中午之前
I'm gonna write 200 tickets. Before noon.
随时停车
中午之前200张
Two hundred tickets before noon!
201张
201.
看着点路  狐狸
Hey, watch where you're going, fox!
他去哪了
Where'd he go?
我不知道你大白天的
Listen. I know what you're doing
出来晃悠什么呢
skulking around during daylight hours,
但我不想惹麻烦  快走吧
but I don't want any trouble in here. So hit the road!
我也不是想找麻烦的
I'm not looking for any trouble either, sir...
我只想买个大冰棍  给我儿子
I simply wanna buy a Jumbo-Pop. For my little boy.
要红的还是蓝的
You want the red, or the blue, pal?
我真是
I'm such a...
行了  孩子  回去吧
Oh, come on, kid. Back up.
-听我说  -怎么了
- Listen, buddy. - What?
你那边没有给狐狸开的冰淇淋店吗
There aren't any fox ice cream joints in your part of town?
有啊  有  只是我儿子
No, no. There are, there are. It's just, my boy,
这只小傻狐狸  特别迷大象
this goofy little stinker, he loves all things elephant.
长大了也想当大象
He wants to be one when he grows up.
多可爱啊
Isn't that adorable?
我怎么忍心让他梦想破灭呢
Who the heck am I to crush his little dreams, huh? Right?
你是不识字吗  狐狸  看这个
Look, you probably can't read, fox, but the sign says
我们有权拒绝提供服务
we reserve the right to refuse service to anyone!
快走吧
So beat it.
后面都等着呢
You're holding up the line.
你好  不好意思
Hello. Excuse me.
你也和其他人一样
Hey, you're gonna have to
得排队等着  交通协管
wait your turn like everyone else, meter maid.
其实我是警员
Actually, I'm an officer.
就问一下
Just have a quick question.
你的顾客们知道
Are your customers aware they're getting
吃的饼干和冰淇淋里有鼻涕吗
snot and mucus with their cookies and cream?
你说什么呢
What are you talking about?
我不想惹麻烦
Well. I don't wanna cause you any trouble,
但是不戴鼻套盛冰淇淋
but I believe scooping ice cream with
是严重违反健康条例的
an ungloved trunk is a class 3 health code violation.
这也不是小事了
Which is kind of a big deal.
当然  如果你肯戴上
Of course I could let you off
我是可以给你个警告了事
with a warning if you were to glove those trunks
而且  还得给这位
and... I don't know... finish selling this...
爸爸和他儿子  卖一根  什么
nice dad and his son a... What was it?
大冰棒  拜托了
A Jumbo-Pop. Please.
大冰棒
A Jumbo-Pop.
-15块  -非常感谢  谢谢你
- $15. - Thank you so much. Thank you.
不会吧
Oh no, are you kidding me...
忘带钱包了
I don't have my wallet!
真是就差忘带脑袋了
I'd lose my head if it weren't attached to my neck.
真是啊  天哪  不好意思
That's the truth. Oh, boy. I'm sorry, pal.
大概是你最糟的生日了
Gotta be about the worst birthday ever.
别生我的气  谢谢你
Please don't be mad at me. Thanks anyway.
不用找了
Keep the change.
警官  真是感恩戴德
Officer, I can't thank you enough.
太好了  怎么回报你啊
So kind. Really. Can I pay you back?
不用  我请了
Oh, no. My treat.
主要是听到别人
It's just, you know it burns me up
对狐狸有偏见我就受不了
to see folks with such backward attitudes towards foxes.
我只是想说
I just want to say you're
你是位好父亲  口才真棒
a great dad and just a real articulate fella.
真是过奖了
Well, that is high praise.
我也很少遇到不看低我的人
It's rare that I find someone so non-patronizing.
-警官你叫  -霍普斯  你是
- Officer? - Hopps. Mr..?
王尔德  尼克·王尔德
Wilde. Nick Wilde.
你呢  小家伙  长大了想做大象吗
And you, little guy. You wanna be an elephant when you grow up?
那就去做大象好了  这是动物城
You be an elephant. Because this is Zootopia.
谁都能成就无限可能
Anyone can be anything.
我总这么跟他说
I tell him that all the time.
好了  给你  双爪抱住
All right, here you go. Two paws.
看这笑脸  生日快乐真开心
Yeah. Oh, look at that smile, that's a happy birthday smile!
好了  嘟嘟两声道个别吧
All right, give her a little bye-bye toot-toot.
-再见了  -再见
- Bye, now! - Goodbye!
小大象
Hey, little toot-toot...
鼠曼兄弟银行
爪子冰棍
Pawpsicles.
来吃爪子冰棍
Get your Pawpsicles.
爪子冰棍
-木材送到了  -怎么这个颜色
- Lumber delivery. - What's with the color?
颜色  这是红木
The color? Uh... it's redwood.
39, 40, there you go.
装小孩真厉害  大家伙
Way to work that diaper, big guy.
不跟爸爸吻别吗
No kiss bye-bye for daddy?
再敢亲我  我把你脸咬下来
You kiss me tomorrow, I'll bite your face off!
再见
Ciao.
我为你出头  你却骗了我
Well, I stood up for you, and you lied to me.
骗子
You liar!
这叫智取  亲爱的
It's called a hustle, Sweetheart.
我可不是骗子  他才是
And I'm not the liar. He is.
好了  狡猾的尼克  你被捕了
All right, Slick-Nick. You're under arrest.
真的吗  为什么
Really? For what?
我也不清楚  无证经营食品吗
Gee, I don't know. How about selling food without a permit?
跨区运输未申报商品
Transporting undeclared commerce across borough lines?
-虚假广告  -许可证  商品申报凭证
- False advertizing. - Permit. Receipt of declared commerce.
我没做虚假广告  再会
And I didn't falsely advertize anything. Take care.
你跟老鼠说冰棒棍是红木的
You told that mouse the Pawpsicle sticks were redwood!
是啊  红色的木头  简称就是
That's right. Red wood. With a space in the middle.
红木
Wood that is red.
你动不了我的  萝卜头
You can't touch me, Carrots.
我从小就开始这么干了
I've been doing this since I was born.
不许再叫我萝卜头
You're gonna wanna refrain from calling me Carrots.
我的错  我只是觉得你
My bad. I just naturally assumed you came...
肯定是从遍地胡萝卜的屯里来的吧
from some little carrot-choked Podunk. No?
不不
Uh, no.
鹿溪才是屯  我在兔窝镇长大
Podunk is in Deerbrooke county and I grew up in Bunnyburrow.
来听听这个故事你熟不熟
Okay. Tell me if this story sounds familiar.
天真的小山妞成绩好  有理想
Naive little hick with good grades and big ideas
就觉得  我得去动物城
decides "Hey, look at me, I'm gonna move to Zootopia...
食肉和食草动物和平相处  还一起唱山歌
where predators and prey live in harmony and sing Kumbaya!"
结果呢  哎呀  他们关系并不好
Only to find, whoopsie, we don't all get along.
做大城市警察的梦想
And that dream of becoming a big city cop,
哎呀呀  成了交通协管
double whoopsie, she's a meter maid.
还有哎呀呀呀
And whoopsie number three-sie,
没人关心她和她的梦想
no one cares about her or her dreams.
梦想很快就破灭了
And soon enough those dreams die,
然后身体和精神都消沉下去
and our bunny sinks into emotional and literal squalor
只能住在桥洞里
living in a box under a bridge.
终于发现自己只能选择回家
Till finally she has no choice but to go back home
夹着自己那条
with that cute fuzzy wuzzy
毛茸茸的小尾巴  变成了
little tail between her legs to become...
你是兔窝镇的  对吧
You're from Bunnyburrow, is that what you said?
种胡萝卜的农民
So how about a carrot farmer?
听着不错吧
That sound about right?
小心点  不然就不止是你的梦想被碾碎了
Be careful now, or it won't just be your dreams getting crushed.
没人能告诉我做什么不做什么
No one tells me what I can or can't be.
尤其是个没胆量的混球
Especially not some jerk who never had the guts to
只知道智取爪子冰棍
try to be anything more than a Pawpsicle hustler.
好了
All right, look.
大家来到动物城
Everyone comes to Zootopia
觉得能成就无限可能
thinking they can be anything they want.
其实不行  你只能成为自己
Well, you can't. You can only be what you are.
狐狸狡猾  兔子蠢
Sly fox. Dumb bunny.
我不蠢
I'm not a dumb bunny.
好吧  这也不是湿水泥
Right. And that's not wet cement.
你做不了真正的警察的
You'll never be a real cop.
做交通协管倒是挺不错
You're a cute meter maid, though.
没准能做督察员呢  加油
Maybe a supervisor one day. Hang in there.
爸爸妈妈
一人份胡萝卜
-爸爸妈妈  -看她  亲爱的
- Oh, hey, it's my parents! - Oh, there she is! Hi, Sweetheart!
你好啊  厉害的朱迪
Hey there, Jude the Dude.
第一天做警察怎么样
How was your first day on the force?
-可棒了  -跟想的一样吗
- It was real great! - Yeah? Everything you ever hoped?
当然了  还有呢
Absolutely. And more.
大家都可好了  我觉得
Everyone's so nice, and I feel like...
自己真的有点成就
I'm really making a difference.
等等  天哪  邦妮
Wait a second. Holy cranks, Bonnie.
-看看  -我的天哪
- Look at that! - Oh, my sweet heaven!
朱迪  你是交通协管吗
Judy, are you a meter maid?
这个  只是暂时的
Oh, this.. No! Oh, no. This is just a temporary thing..
-警局最安全的工作  -她不是真警察
- It's the safest job on the force! - She's not a real cop!
-祈祷终于有回音了  -赞美主
- Our prayers have been answered! - Glorious day!
交通协管  交通协管  交通协管
Ho-ho, meter maid, meter maid, meter maid!
-爸爸  爸爸  -交通协管
- Dad! Dad! - Meter maid!
今天很漫长了  我得
You know what, it's been a really long day, I should...
-你休息吧  -好好协管交通去吧
- You get some rest. - Those meters aren't gonna maid themselves.
-再见  -再见
- Bye-bye. - Bye-bye.
兔子  快关了那丧气的歌
Hey, bunny! Turn down that depressing music!
别烦交通协管  没听她说话吗
Leave the meter maid alone, didn't you hear her conversation?
-她觉得自己是废物  -闭嘴
- She feels like a failure! - Oh, shut up!
-你闭嘴  -你闭嘴
- You shut up! - You shut up!
-你闭嘴  -明天又是新的一天
- You shut up! - Tomorrow is another day.
是啊  还可能更糟呢
Yeah, but it might be worse!
我才超了30秒
I was 30 seconds over!
你真厉害  姑娘
Yeah, you're a real hero, lady.
我妈妈说她想让你去死
My mommy says she wishes you were dead.
土包子  我交的税养的你
Uncool rabbit, my tax dollars pay your salary.
我是真的警察  我是真的警察
I am a real cop. I am a real cop.
你  兔子
Hey, you! Bunny!
先生  您如果有意见
Sir, if you have a grievance
可以去交通法庭起诉
you may contest recitation in traffic court.
你说什么呢  我的店
What are you talking about?! My shop!
刚被抢了  看  他跑了
It was just robbed! Look, he's getting away!
你是警察吗
Well, are you a cop or not?
是啊  是啊  不用担心  先生  交给我
Yes! Yes! Don't worry, sir, I got this!
站住
Stop!
我是警察  站住
Stop in the name of the law!
来抓我啊  毛尾巴
Catch me if ya' can, cottontail!
小心
Coming through!
我是麦克角警官  发现违法行为
This is officer McHorn. We got a 10-31.
交给我  霍普斯警官  我在追了
I got dibs! Officer Hopps, I am in pursuit!
小啮齿城
你  站住
You! Freeze!
交通协管  等真的警察来吧
Hey, meter maid! Wait for the real cops!
字幕
Stop!
抱歉  借过  抱歉  对不起
Sorry! Coming through. Excuse me. Excuse me. Pardon.
再见了  平脚怪
Bon voyage, flatfoot!
-站住  -吃个甜甜圈吧  条子
- Stop right there! - Have a donut, coppa!
大甜甜圈
老鼠家饭店
天哪  看到那豹纹打底裤了吗
Oh my god, did you see those leopard print jeggings?
-发型好棒  -谢谢
- I love your hair. - Thank you.
来找爸爸吧
Come to papa!
好了  您得跟其他人一眼排队
Okay. You're gonna have to be patient and wait in line
耐心等  水獭顿太太  好吗
just like everyone else, Mrs. Otterton. Okay?
-黄鼠狼上门了  -霍普斯
- I popped the weasel! - Hopps!
牛局长
擅离职守  引发公众恐慌
Abandoning your post. Inciting a scurry.
危及啮齿动物生命
Reckless endangerment of rodents...
但说句公道话
But, to be fair,
你确实阻止了个恶棍
you did stop a master criminal
偷走两袋发霉的洋葱
from stealing two dozen moldy onions.
抱歉  长官  这些不是洋葱
Hate to disagree with you, sir, but those aren't onions.
这些是藏红花属植物  午夜嚎叫[拉丁文]
Those are a crocus variety called midnicampum holicithias.
是C类药用植物  长官
They're a class C botanical, sir.
我家那里
Well, I grew up in a family
都流行种植业
where plant husbandry was kind of a thing...
-闭上你的小嘴  -长官  我抓住了坏人
- Shut your tiny mouth now! - Sir, I got the bad guy.
这是我的工作
That's my job.
你的工作是开违章停车罚单
Your job is putting tickets on parked cars!
局长  水獭顿夫人又来找你了
Chief, Mrs. Otterton's here to see you again.
-现在不行  -我只想知道你是不是
- Not now. - Okay, I just need to know if you want to...
-这次见见  她好像挺伤心  -现在不行
- take it this time she seems really upset... - Not now!
长官  我不想做交通协管
Sir. I don't wanna be a meter maid,
我想做真的警察
I wanna be a real cop.
你以为市长把你分过来时
Do you think the mayor asked what I wanted...
-问过我想要什么吗  -可是  长官
- when he assigned you to me? - But, sir...
生活不是卡通音乐剧
Life isn't some cartoon musical
只要唱唱跳跳的  然后无聊的梦
where you sing a little song, and your insipid dreams...
就奇迹般地成真了  放手吧
magically come true! So let it go.
牛局长  拜托了  五分钟就好
Chief Bogo, please! Five minutes of your time, please.
抱歉  长官  我想拦住她  但是太滑了
I'm sorry sir. I tried to stop her, she's super slippery.
我得坐一坐
I gotta go sit down.
夫人  我说了  我们已经尽力了
Ma'am, as I've told you, we're doing everything we can.
我丈夫失踪十天了
My husband has been missing for ten days.
-他叫艾米特·水獭顿  -我知道
- His name is Emmitt Otterton. - Yes. I know.
是花匠  我们有两个孩子
He's a florist. We have 2 beautiful children.
他不会凭空消失的
He would never just disappear.
夫人  我们的警探都很忙
Ma'am, our detectives are very busy.
拜托了  肯定有人能找到艾米特的
Please. There's gotta be somebody to find my Emmitt.
-水獭顿夫人  -我能找到
- Mrs. Otterton. - I will find him.
谢谢你  保佑你  小兔子
Thank you! Bless you, bless you, little bunny!
拿着这个  找到我的艾米特
Take this. Find my Emmitt.
带他回来见我和孩子们  摆脱了
Bring him home to me and my babies. Please.
水獭顿夫人  请在外面等
Mrs. Otterton. Please wait out here.
好啊  太感谢你们两个了
Of course. Oh, thank you both so much!
稍等
One second.
-你被炒了  -什么  为什么
- You're fired. - What? Why?
违抗命令  我要打开门
Insubordination! Now. I'm going to open this door,
然后你告诉那水獭
and you're going to tell that Otter
你之前是交通协管  有严重妄想症
you're a former meter maid with delusion of grandeur,
不能接这个案子
who will not be taking the case.
我听说霍普斯警官接了案子
I just heard Officer Hopps is taking the case!
头羊市长助理
Assistant Mayor Bellwether!
哺乳动物选拔行动真的有了成效
The Mammal Inclusion Initiative is really starting to pay off.
狮心市长肯定高兴坏了
Mayor Lionheart is just gonna be so jazzed!
先别告诉市长吧
No, let's not tell the mayor just yet.
信息发送成功  好了
And I sent it, and it is done, so I did do that.
我觉得这下案子有把握了
All right, well, I'd say the case is in good hands.
我们小动物就得互相照应
Us little guys really need to stick together, right?
-才能羊眉兔气  -真逗
- Like glue. - Good one.
有问题就打我电话  好吗
Just call me if you ever need anything. Okay?
我就是你在市政厅的朋友
You've always got a friend at City Hall,
好了  朱迪  再见
Judy. All right! Bye-bye!
谢谢你  女士
Thank you, ma'am!
我给你48小时
I will give you 48 hours.
太棒了
Yes!
-也就是两天时间内找到艾米特·水獭顿  -好
- That's two days to find Emmitt Otterton. - Okay.
但是找不到  你就得辞职
But...you strike out, you resign.
好吧  成交
Okay. Deal.
很好  爪豪斯会把完整的案宗给你
Splendid. Clawhauser will give you the complete case file.
给你  失踪的水獭
Here you go. One missing otter.
动物城警局
失踪哺乳动物报告
-就这么点  -就是说呀
- That's it? - Yikes!
这是我见过的最薄的案宗了  线索  无
That is the smallest case file I've ever seen. Leads, none.
目击证人  无
Witnesses, none.
而且你现在还进不了电脑系统  所以
And you're not in the computer system yet, so...
资源  无
Resources, none!
希望你没把自己的前途
Hoo, I hope you didn't stake your career
都赌在这个案子上
on cracking this one.
好吧  最后出现的地点
Okay. Last known sighting.
最后出现地点
可以借我用一下吗  谢谢
Can I just borrow? Thank you.
-爪子冰棒  -作案凶器
- Pawpsicle? - The murder weapon!
-"来尝尝爪子冰棒"  -没错  因为那
- "Get your Pawpsicle"... - Yeah! Cause that...
那是什么意思
What does that mean?
意思是我有线索了
It means I have a lead.
-你好  又是我  -是嘟嘟警官啊
- Hi! Hello! It's me again! - Hey! It's Officer Toot-Toot.
不  我是霍普斯警官
No. Actually it's Officer Hopps,
我要问你几个问题  是关于一个案子的
and I'm here to ask you some questions about a case.
怎么了  交通协管
What happened, meter maid?
有人把交通锥标偷走了吗
Did someone steal a traffic cone?
不是我干的
It wasn't me.
萝卜头  你会把宝宝吵醒的
Hey, Carrots, you're gonna wake the baby.
我要去工作了
I gotta get to work.
这很重要  先生
This is important, sir.
你那十块钱的爪子冰棒可以等一会再卖
I think your ten dollars worth of Pawpsicles can wait.
小家伙  我一天挣两百块呢
I make 200 bucks a day, fluff.
从我12岁起  一年365天无休
365 days a year, since I was 12.
时间就是金钱  让开
And time is money. Hop along.
请你看一下这张照片
Please just look at the picture.
水獭顿先生手里的爪子冰棒是你卖给他的吧
You sold Mr. Otterton that Pawpsicle, right?
-你认识他吗  -没有我不认识的人
- Do you know him? - I know everybody.
而且我还知道某处的一家玩具店
And I also know that somewhere
丢了一个毛绒玩具
there's a toy store missing its stuffed animal,
所以你赶紧回盒子里待着吧
so why don't you get back to your box?
好吧  看来你是敬酒不吃吃罚酒
Fine. Then we'll have to do this the hard way.
你把我的婴儿车锁住了吗
Did you just boot my stroller?
尼古拉斯·王尔德  你被捕了
Nicholas Wilde, you are under arrest.
理由呢  伤害你的感情吗
For what? Hurting your feelings?
偷税漏税
Felony tax evasion.
从你12岁开始  每年365天
Yeah.. 200 dollars a day, 365 days a year,
每天200块
since you were 12...
一共是20年  所以乘以20
that's two decades, so times twenty,
也就是146万  应该没错吧
which is 1,460,000, I think.
虽然我只是只蠢兔子
I mean, I am just a dumb bunny,
不过我们很会算数[繁殖]
but we are good at multiplying.
总而言之  在你的税务报表上
Anyway, according to your tax forms,
你申报了  让我看看  零元的税
you reported, let me see here, zero!
倒霉的是
Unfortunately,
税收表格上作假是重罪
lying on a federal form is a punishable offense.
-要判刑5年  -空口无凭
- 5 years jail time. - Well, it's my word against yours.
小家伙  从我12岁起
200 bucks a day, fluff,
每年365天  每天200块
365 days a year, since I was twelve.
其实呢  我都录下来了
Actually it's your word against yours.
如果你想要这支笔  你就得帮我找到
And if you want this pen you're going to help me
这只失踪的水獭  不然的话
find this poor missing otter, or the only place
你就只能在监狱的食堂里卖冰棒了
you'll be selling Pawpsicles is the prison cafeteria.
这叫智取  亲爱的
It's called a hustle, sweet heart.
她把你给耍了
She hustled you.
好个智取
She hustled you good!
你现在是警察了  尼克
You're a cop now, Nick.
给你张贴纸  你会用得上的
You're gonna need one of these.
祝你和小毛球合作愉快
Have fun working with the fuzz!
开始交代吧
Start talking.
我不知道他在哪  我只看到他往哪去了
I don't know where he is, I only saw where he went.
棒极了  走吧
Great, let's go!
那地方可不适合可爱的小兔兔
It's not exactly a place for a cute little bunny.
-不许说我可爱  上车  -好吧  你说了算
- Don't call me cute, get in the car. - Okay. You're the boss.
你好
Hi. Hello?
我是  你好
I'm... Hello?
你好  你好
Hello? Hello?
你好  我是
Hello! My name is...
我现在就得打断你
You know, I'm gonna hit the pause button right there.
因为我们不需要兔子童子军曲奇饼了
Cause we're all good on bunny scout cookies.
不
Uh, no.
我是动物城警局的霍普斯警官
I'm Officer Hopps, ZPD.
我在寻找一只失踪的哺乳动物
I'm looking for a missing mammal...
艾米特·水獭顿  就是这位
Emmitt Otterton. Right here.
他曾经是这里的常客
He may have frequented this establishment?
没错  老艾米特
Yeah, old Emmitt!
好几周没见到他了
Haven't seen him in a couple of weeks.
但是  你应该找他的瑜伽教练谈谈
But hey, you should talk to his yoga instructor.
我很乐意带你们到后面去
I'd be happy to take you back.
非常感谢
Oh, thank you so much,
真是非常非常感谢你  这真是
I'd appericiate that more than you can imagine, it'd be such...
你没穿衣服
Oh! You are naked..
当然  我们这里是自然主义俱乐部
Oh, for sure. We're a naturalist club!
没错  在动物城谁都能成就无限可能
Yeah. In Zootopia anyone can be anything.
这些人  他们就喜欢光着
These guys, they be naked.
南吉就在欢乐池的另一边
Nangi's just on the other side of the Pleasure Pool.
天啊  这里让你觉得别扭吗
Oh boy. Does this make you uncomfortable?
因为你要是觉得别扭的话  现在放弃还不丢人
Because if so, there's no shame in calling it quits.
很丢人
Yes, there is.
这才像话
Boy, that's the spirit.
没错  有些哺乳动物认为自然主义很奇怪
Yeah, some mammals say the naturalist life is weird.
可你知道什么才是奇怪吗
But you know what I say is weird?
动物穿衣服才奇怪呢  找到她了
Clothes on animals! Here we go!
你们也看到了  南吉是头大象
As you can see, Nangi is an elephant,
所以她一定会记得所有细节
so she'll totally remember everything.
南吉
Hey, Nangi.
他们要问你几个水獭艾米特的问题
These dudes have some questions about Emmitt the otter.
谁
Who?
艾米特·水獭顿
Emmitt Otterton.
他上你的瑜伽课上了六年了
Been coming to your yoga class for like six years.
我不记得这只河狸
I have no memory of this beaver.
其实他是只水獭
He's an otter, actually.
他几周前的周三来过  记得吗
He was here a couple of Wednesdays ago. Remember?
不记得
No.
他穿了一件绿色的针织毛衣背心
Yeah, he was wearing a green cable knit sweater vest,
还有一条新买的夸特卫宽松裤
and a new pair of Quarterway slacks.
还系了条佩斯利花纹领带  漂亮的温莎结
Oh, and a Paisley tie, sweet Windsor knot.
-可帅了  记得吗  南吉  -不记得
- Real tight. Remember that, Nangi? - No.
没错  咱们俩一块送他出去的
Yeah, and we both walked him out,
然后他上了一辆银边的白色旧车
and he got into this big old white car with a silver trim.
那车该送修了
Needed a tune up.
第三个汽缸都不打火了  记得吗  南吉
The third cylinder wasn't firing. Remember that, Nangi?
不记得
No.
你不会恰好记得车牌号码吧
You didn't happen to catch the licence plate number?
-记得吗  -当然
- Did you? - Oh, for sure.
车牌是29THD03
It was 2-9-T-H-D-0-3.
03  你提供了很多有用的信息  谢谢
0-3. Wow, this is a lot of great info. Thank you.
我就说南吉的记忆力好的很嘛
Told you Nangi has a mind like a steel trap.
真希望我也能有大象这么好的记忆力
I wish I had a memory like an elephant.
迷泉绿洲
我玩的很开心  你就不用谢我了
Well, I had a ball. You are welcome for the clue.
既然傻瓜都能查到车牌号码
And seeing as any moron can run a plate,
那么我就拿上笔跟你道别了
I will take that pen and bid you adieu.
车牌号  我查不了车牌号
The plate. I can't run a plate.
我还进不了电脑系统
I'm not in the system yet.
-请把笔给我  -你刚才说什么
- Give me the pen, please. - What was it you said?
傻瓜都能查车牌号
Any moron can run a plate?
要是这里有个傻瓜
Gosh, if only there were a moron around
能干这件事就好了
who were up to the task.
兔子  我已经照你说的做了
Rabbit, I did what you asked.
你不能永远抓着我不放
You can't keep me on the hook forever.
不会永远的
Not forever.
我只剩36个小时来破案了
Well, I only have 36 hours left to solve this case.
你到底能不能查车牌号
So can you run the plate or not?
我刚想起来  我有个朋友在车管所工作
Actually, I just remembered, I have a pal at the DMV.
车管所
闪电是这里最快的人
Flash is the fastest guy in there.
你要办事  找他就对了
You need something done, he's on it.
希望如此
I hope so.
我们的时间真的很紧  每一分钟都很重要
We are really fighting the clock and every minute counts.
等等  他们全都是树獭吗
Wait. They're all sloths?
你说会很快的
You said this was going to be quick!
怎么  就因为他是树獭
What, are you saying just because he's a sloth
他就快不起来吗
he can't be fast?
不是谁都能成就无限可能吗
I thought in Zootopia anyone could be anything.
闪电  闪电  数你最快
Flash, Flash, Hundred Yard Dash!
哥们  见到你真高兴
Buddy, it's nice to see you.
我也  很高兴  见到你
Nice to... see you... too.
闪电  给你介绍一下我的朋友
Hey, Flash, I'd love you to meet my friend.
亲爱的  我忘了你叫什么名字了
Ah... Darlin, I've forgotten your name.
我是朱迪·霍普斯警官  你好吗
Officer Judy Hopps, ZPD. How are you?
我
I am...
过得
doing... just..
-挺好  -还  不错
- Fine? - As well..as..I can..be...
-有什么  -坚持住
- What... - Hang in there.
-可以  -我希望你可以帮我查一个车牌
- can I...do... - Well, I was hoping you could run a plate...
-帮你  -我希望你可以
- for you... - Well, I was hoping you could...
的吗
...today?
我希望你可以帮我们查一个车牌号码
Well, I was hoping you could run a plate for us.
我们真的很着急
We are in a really big hurry.
-当然  车牌号码  是  -29T
- Sure... What's the...plate... - 2-9-T...
-什么  -29THD03
- number? - 2-9-T-H-D-0-3.
-29  -THD03
- 2...9... - T-H-D-0-3.
-T  -HD03
- T... - H-D-0-3.
-H  -D03
- H... - D-0-3.
-D  -03
- D... - 0-3.
-0  -3
- 0... - 3!
-闪电  想听个笑话吗  -不要
- Hey, Flash. Wanna hear a joke? - No!
好啊
Sure.
骆驼为什么会有三个驼峰
What do you call a three-humped camel?
我不知道  骆驼为什么
I don't know. What do you call...
-有三个驼峰  -会  有  三个驼峰
- Three-humped camel. - A three-humped...camel?
怀孕了
Pregnant.
哈哈  没错  很好笑  很好笑
Ha ha. Yes, very funny, very funny!
我们能不能认真工作
Can we please just focus on the task?
等等  等等
Wait, wait!
-普莉希拉  -不
- Priscilla! - Oh, no!
-什么事  闪电  -骆驼
- Yes...Flash? - What...do..
-不  -为什么会有
- No... - you call...
三个驼峰
A three-humped camel?
怀孕了  好了  棒极了  我们知道了
Pregnant! Okay! Great! We got it!
-求求你  -三个驼峰
- Please just... - three...humped...
动物城哺乳动物车管所
车牌号  29THD03
车主  冰原镇豪华轿车服务公司
地址  动物城冰原镇755常青街
-给  -好的  好的  快  谢谢
- Here...you... - Yes! Yeah, yeah! Hurry, thank you!
-29THD03  -你
- 2-9-T-H-D-0-3. - ...go.
注册在病源镇豪华轿车服务公司
It's registered to Tundratown Limo Service.
水獭顿坐豪华轿车走了  这辆车在病源镇
A limo took Otterton! And the limo's in Tundratown!
就在病源镇
It's in Tundratown!
好个智取  哥们  我爱你  我欠你的
Way to hustle, bud. I love you. I owe you.
快走  我们得赶在下班高峰期前
Hurry! We gotta beat the rush hour and...
已经是晚上了
It's night?!
锁门了  棒极了
Closed. Great.
冰原镇豪华轿车服务公司
我敢说你没有搜索令吧
And I will betcha you don't have a warrant to get in, hmm?
-该死  真是扫兴  -你故意把耽误了我一天
- Darn it. It's a bummer. - You wasted the day on purpose.
女士  我戴着假警徽
Ma'am, I have a fake badge.
我绝不会妨碍你假装调查的
I would never impede your pretend investigation.
这不是假装调查
It's not a pretend investigation!
看  看到他了吗  这只水獭失踪了
Look, see? See him? This otter is missing.
那他们应该派个真警察去找他
Well, then they should have gotten a real cop to find him.
你什么毛病  看到我失败
What is your problem? Does seeing me fail
能让你对自己悲哀的生活感觉好些吗
somehow make you feel better about your own sad, miserable life?
是的  当然了
It does, 100 %.
既然你没有搜索令
Now, since you're sans warrant.
那咱们两清了吧
I guess we're done?
好吧  两清了  给你笔
Fine. We are done. Here's your pen.
首先  你丢东西的动作真像兔子
First off, you throw like a bunny.
其次  你真是个输不起的家伙
Second, you're a very sore loser.
回头见了  毛茸茸警官  可惜都结束了
See you later, Officer Fluff. So sad this is over.
真希望能多帮上你点忙
I wish I could have helped more.
问题是
The thing is,
有正经的理由  就不需要搜查令
you don't need a warrant if you have probable cause,
我非常确定我见到了
and I'm pretty sure I saw a...
一只贼眉鼠眼的家伙翻过了栅栏
shifty lowlife climbing the fence.
所以你还真帮了不少忙  走吧
So you're helping plenty! Come on!
29THD03  就是这辆了
2-9-T-H-D-0-3! This is it!
北极熊毛
Polar bear fur.
-天啊  -什么  怎么了
- Oh my God! - What? What?
杰里·沃尔的《丝绒烟斗》
The Velvety Pipes of Jerry Vole!
但是是CD  现在谁还听CD啊
But on CD. Who still uses CDs?
萝卜头  如果水獭在这待过  他肯定非常难受
Carrots, if your otter was here, he had a very bad day.
那些是爪痕
Those are claw marks.
你见过这样的情况吗
You ever seen anything like this?
-没有  -等下  看
- No. - Oh, wait. Look!
是他  艾米特·水獭顿  他肯定来过这儿
This is him. Emmitt Otterton. He was definitely here.
你觉得出了什么事
What do you think happened?
不好  等一下  北极熊毛
Oh no, wait a minute. Polar bear fur...
鼠帮音乐  高档杯子
Rat-pack music. Fancy cup.
我知道这是谁的车了  赶快走
I know whose car this is, we gotta go!
什么  是谁的车
What? Whose car is it?
冰原镇里最可怕的黑帮老大
The most feared crime boss in Tundratown.
他叫大先生
They call him Mr. Big,
他不喜欢我  所以我们快走吧
and he does not like me. So we gotta go!
我不走  这是犯罪现场
I'm not leaving, this is a crime scene.
要是大先生发现我在这儿
Well, it's gonna be an even bigger crime scene...
就会变成更惨烈的犯罪现场
if Mr. Big finds me here,
马上走
so we're leaving right now.
雷蒙德  那是凯文吧  好久不见
Raymond! And is that Kevin? Long time, no see.
提到"不见"  你们就当没见过我行吗
And speaking of no see, how about you forget you saw me?
看在往日的情面上
For old times sake?
不行
That's a no.
你做了什么  让大先生这么生气
What did you do that made Mr. Big so mad at you?
可能是因为我曾经卖给他一块昂贵的壁毯
I, uh... I may have sold him a very expensive wall rug
它是用臭鼬屁股上的毛做的
that was made from the fur of a skunk's butt.
我的天啊
Oh, sweet cheese 'n crackers.
-那是大先生吗  -不
- Is that Mr. Big? - No.
-那他呢  是他吗  -不是
- What about him? Is that him? - No.
-这回肯定是他  -别说了
- That's gotta be him. - Stop talking.
别说了  别说了
Stop talking. Stop talking!
大先生  这只是一次单纯的误会
Mr. Big, sir, this is a simple misunder...
好
Yeah.
这只是一次单纯的误会而已
This is a simple misunderstanding.
我女儿结婚这天
You come here unannounced
你不请自来
on the day my daughter is to be married.
其实  我们是被人强行带到这儿的  所以...
Well, actually, we were brought here against our will, so...
关键是  我之前不知道那是您的车
Point is, I did not know that it was your car,
我也不知道您女儿要结婚
and I certainly did not know about your daughter's wedding!
我信任过你  尼克
I trusted you, Nicky.
我邀请你来我家
I welcomed you into my home.
我们还共进晚餐
We broke bread together.
奶奶给你做了奶油煎饼卷
Grandmama made you a cannoli.
结果你怎么报答我的好意的
And how did you repay my generosity?
拿一块臭鼬屁股毛做的毯子报答我
With a rug made from the butt of a skunk.
臭鼬屁股毛皮做的毯子
A skunk-butt rug.
你不尊重我
You disrespected me.
你不尊重我奶奶
You disrespected my grandmama,
我用那块臭鼬屁股毛皮毯子埋葬了她
who I buried in that skunk-butt rug.
我告诉过你  不准再到这儿来了
I told you never to show your face here again,
但你还是来了
but here you are.
贼眉鼠眼地  跟这个
Snooping around with this...
你是干什么的  演员吗  穿成那样干什么
What are you? A performer? What's with the costume?
-先生  我是警... -哑剧演员
- Sir, I am a co... - Mime!
她是哑剧演员  哑剧演员不能说话
She's a mime. This mime can not speak.
-你是哑剧演员  你不能说话  -不  我是警察
- You can't speak if you're a mime. - No, I am a cop.
我在查艾米特·水獭顿案
And I'm on the Emmitt Otterton case.
线索指向了你的车
And my evidence puts him in your car!
随便你怎么威胁我
So intimidate me all you want,
就算这是我这辈子做的最后一件事
I'm going to find out what you did to that otter
我也要查出你把水獭怎么样了
if it's the last thing I do.
那我就只剩一个请求了
Then I have only one request.
帮我跟奶奶问好
Say hello to Grandmama.
做了他们
Ice 'em!
不不不  我什么也没看见  我绝不说出去
No, no, no. I didn't see nothing! I'm not saying nothing!
你也不会说出去了
And you never will.
求求你  别别别
Please! No, no, no, no!
你要是因为毯子生我的气  我还有更多毯子
If you're mad at me about the rug, I've got more rugs!
爸爸  我们该跳舞了
Daddy! It's time for our dance!
我们不是说好了吗  婚礼上不能做掉谁
What did we say? No icing anyone at my wedding!
我不得不这么做  宝贝  爸爸也无奈
I have to, baby, daddy has to.
-做掉他们  -不不不
- Ice 'em. - No, no, no!
等下  等下
Wait, wait!
她就是昨天从巨型甜甜圈下
She's the bunny that saved my life yesterday!
救了我一命的兔子
From that giant donut!
-这只兔子吗  -对  你好
- This bunny? - Yeah. Hi!
-你好  我喜欢你的裙子  -谢谢
- Hi. I love your dress. - Thank you.
放下他们
Put them down.
你帮了我大忙
You've done me a great service.
我会帮你找到水獭
I will help you find the otter.
我感谢你的善良  我要报答你
I will take your kindness, and pay it forward.
水獭顿是我的花匠  他就像家人一样
Otterton is my florist. He's like a part of the family.
他说有要事想商量
He had something important he wanted to discuss.
所以我派那辆车去接他
That's why I sent that car to pick him up.
但他没能到这儿来
But he never arrived.
因为他受到了袭击
Because he was attacked.
不  是他袭击别人
No, he attacked.
水獭顿吗
Otterton?
就是水獭顿
Otterton.
他发疯了  在车里闹了个底朝天
He went crazy. Ripped up the car.
把我的司机吓得半死
Scared my driver half to death.
然后消失在夜色中
And disappeared into the night.
可他是一只可爱的水獭
But he's a sweet little otter.
孩子  就算我们进化了
My child, we may be evolved,
内心深处也还是动物
but deep down we are still animals.
你想找到水獭顿  就去跟司机谈谈
You wanna find Otterton, talk to the driver of the car.
他叫曼查斯  住在热带雨林区
His name is Manchas. Lives in the Rainforest District.
只有他能告诉你更多消息
Only he can tell you more.
曼查斯先生
Mr. Manchas?
我是警局的朱迪·霍普斯
Judy Hopps, ZPD.
我们想知道艾米特·水獭顿遭遇了什么
We just wanna know what happened to Emmitt Otterton.
你应该问我遭遇了什么
You should be asking what happened to me.
-这是一只小水獭干的  -发生什么了
- A teensy otter did that? - What happened?
他兽性大发
He was an animal.
四爪并用
Down on all fours.
他就是只野兽
He was a savage!
毫无预兆
There was no warning.
他一直喊着午夜嚎叫
He just kept yelling about the Night Howlers.
一遍又一遍地喊午夜嚎叫
Over and over, the Night Howlers!
你也知道午夜嚎叫
So you know about the Night Howlers too?
很好  因为我们来这儿
Good, good. Because the Night Howlers are exactly
就是想跟你谈谈午夜嚎叫  是不是
what we are here to talk about. Right?
对  麻烦你开门  告诉我们你知道什么
Yep, so you just open the door and tell us what you know,
我们也把我们知道的告诉你
and we will tell you what we know.
好不好
Okay?
好吧
Okay.
聪明的狐狸
Clever fox.
曼查斯先生
Mr. Manchas?
你没事吧
Are you okay?
跑  快跑
Run. Run!
-他怎么了  -我不知道
- What is wrong with him?! - I don't know!
跳
Jump!
快跑
Come on!
低头
Head down!
霍普斯警官呼叫
Officer Hopps to dispatch!
你知道夏奇羚吗
Are you familiar with Gazelle?
我们时代最伟大的歌手  长角的天使
Greatest singer of our lifetime. Angel with horns.
接着看  继续看
Okay, hold on. Keep watching.
看她旁边那是谁  是谁
Who's that beside her? Who is it?
你跳得真棒  本杰明·爪豪斯
Wow,You are one hot dancer, Benjamin Clawhauser.
是我  你觉得像真的吗  看起来好真
It's me! Did you think it was real? It looks so real!
其实不是  只是个新应用而已
It's not, it's just a new app.
-等一下  -爪豪斯
- Hold on a second. - Clawhauser!
爪豪斯  听我说
Clawhauser, listen to me.
有危险  美洲豹兽性大发
We have a 10-91! Jaguar gone savage!
-藤蔓和图军加街口  -是图洪加
- Vine and Tujunga!  - It's Tuhunga!
好的  我们马上派后援
Okay, we're sending backup!
霍普斯  霍普斯
Hopps, Hopps!
看  那边  往缆车那儿跑
Look, over there! Head for the sky-trams!
进去  萝卜头  萝卜头
Get in. Carrots? Carrots!
快跑
Go!
哥们  咱食肉动物说句心里话
Buddy, one predator to another.
我能看出你有点紧张
Now I can tell you're a little tense,
我就先给你留点私人空间
so I'm just gonna give you a little personal space!
兔子  不管你干什么  都别松手
Rabbit, whatever you do, do not let go!
-我要松手了  -你要干什么
- I'm gonna let go! - You're gonna to what?
一  二
One, two...
兔子
Rabbit!
萝卜头  你救了我的命
Carrots, you saved my life.
我们警局就是干这个的
Well, that's what we do at the ZPD...
这下可好
Well, this should be good.
我以为只是一起哺乳动物失踪案
I thought this was just a missing mammal case,
可其实要复杂得多
but it's way bigger.
水獭顿先生不仅仅是失踪了
Mr. Otterton did not just disappear.
我认为他和这只美洲豹  他们
I believe he and this jaguar, they...
他们兽性大发了  长官
They went savage, sir.
兽性大发  这不是石器时代了  霍普斯
Savage? This isn't the stone age, Hopps.
动物们不会兽性大发
Animals don't go savage.
我之前也这么想
I thought so too.
但我看到了这个
Till I saw this.
什么
What?
他明明就在这儿
He was right here!
野蛮的美洲豹
The savage jaguar?
长官  我知道自己看到了什么  他差点杀了我们
Sir, I know what I saw. He almost killed us!
或者在兔子眼里
Or maybe any aggressive predator
肉食动物有攻击性就算兽性大发
looks savage to rabbits?
走吧
Let's go!
等等  长官
Wait! Sir!
不只有我看见了他
I'm not the only one who saw him.
尼克
Nick.
你觉得我会相信一只狐狸
You think I'm gonna believe a fox?
他是关键目击证人  我...
Well, he was a key witness, and I...
两天时间找到水獭  不然你就辞职
Two days to find the otter, or you quit.
我们说好的
That was the deal.
警徽
Badge.
-但是长官  我们  -警徽
- But, sir, we had... - Badge!
不行
Uh, no.
你说什么  狐狸
What did you say, fox?
抱歉  我说"不行"
Sorry, what I said was "No...".
她不必给你警徽
She will not be giving you that badge.
你给她一件小丑背心和一辆可笑的三轮车
Look, you gave her a clown vest, and a three-wheeled joke-mobile,
给她两天时间
and two days to solve a case
让她破你们两周都没破的案子
you guys haven't cracked in two weeks?
难怪她会找狐狸帮忙
Yeah, it's no wonder she needed to get help from a fox.
因为你们谁也不打算帮她  是不是
None of you guys were gonna help her, were you?
这样  老大
Here's the thing, chief.
你给她48小时  所以严格来说我们还剩下
You gave her the 48 hours, so technically we still have...
10小时找到水獭顿先生
ten left to find our Mr. Otterton.
而且我们肯定会找到他的
And that's exactly what we're gonna do.
失陪了
So if you'll excuse us,
我们要追查重大线索  还有案子要破
we have a very big lead to follow and a case to crack.
再见
Good day.
霍普斯警官
Officer Hopps.
谢谢
Thank you.
别让他们知道自己能影响到你
Never let them see that they get to you.
这么说...
So...
有人影响过你
Things do get to you?
现在不会了
I mean not, not anymore.
但我曾像你一样弱小
But I was small and emotionally unbalanced
情绪失控
like you once.
-是吗  -不  真的
- Har har. - No, it's true.
我当时大概八九岁
I think I was 8, or maybe 9...
我一心想
And all I wanted to do
加入童子军
was join the Junior Ranger Scouts.
所以我妈妈设法凑够了钱
So my mom scaped together enough money
给我买了一身崭新的制服
to buy me a brand new uniform.
因为我一定要融入进去
Because, by god, I was gonna fit in.
动物城  少年童子军
哪怕我是队里唯一的食肉动物  唯一一只狐狸
Even if I was the only predator in the troop, the only fox.
尼克
Hey, Nick.
我要成为童子军中的一员
I was gonna be part of a pack.
-准备好加入了吗  -当然  生来就准备好了
- Ready for initiation? - Yeah. Pretty much born ready.
我太骄傲了
I was so proud.
举起你的右爪  宣读誓言
Okay. Now raise your right paw, and deliver the oath.
我  尼古拉斯·王尔德  在此起誓
I, Nicholas Wilde, promise to be brave,
我将勇敢忠诚  热心可靠
loyal, helpful and trustworthy.
即使你是只狐狸吗
Even though you're a fox?
什么
What?
不  我做错什么了  各位
No, no! What did I do wrong, you guys?
拜托  我做错了什么了  我干什么了
No, please! What did I do wrong? What did I do?
你以为我们会相信一只不戴口套的狐狸
If you thought we would ever trust a fox without a muzzle?
你比你外表的样子还蠢
You're even dumber than you look.
他是要哭了吗
Is he gonna cry?
那天我学到了两件事
I learned two things that day.
我绝不让别人知道他们影响到了我
One,I was never gonna let anyone see that they got to me.
还有一个呢
And two?
如果整个世界
If the world's only gonna
都觉得狐狸奸诈狡猾
see a fox as shifty and untrustworthy...
那我也没必要变成别的样子了
There's no point in trying to be anything else.
尼克  你不是这样的人
Nick, you are so much more than that.
天哪  瞧瞧下面堵成什么样了
Boy, look at that traffic down there.
问问交通局的查克怎么样
How about we go up to Chuck in traffic central?
查克  道路监控显示情况如何
Chuck, how are things looking on the jam cams?
尼克  我很高兴你告诉了我
Nick, I'm glad you told me.
道路监控
The jam cams...
-真的  你不用岔开话题的  -不不不
- Seriously, it's okay. - No, no no!
整个天篷到处都是道路监控摄像头
There are traffic cameras everywhere. All over the canopy!
不管那只豹子去了哪
Whatever happened to that jaguar...
道路监控都应该拍得到
The traffic cameras would have caught it!
-棒  -哈哈  很狡猾哎  小狐狸
- Bingo! - Ho-ho! Pretty sneaky, slick!
但是  你之前都没法查车牌
However, if you didn't have access to the system before,
恐怕现在牛脾气局长也不会给你查
I doubt chief Buffalo Butt is gonna let you into it now.
确实  但我市政厅的有个朋友也许可以
No. But I have a friend at City Hall who might.
先生  能请您看一下这些重要的账单吗
Sir, if we could just review these very important billings.
先生  抱歉  先生
Sir! Oh, I'm sorry. Sir.
好了  我听到了  头羊
Okay! I heard you, Bellwether,
你处理就行了
just take care of it!
谢谢  取消我下午的事  我要出去
Please. And clear my afternoon, I'm going out.
但是  先生
Oh, no, no.
你还约了动物评级公司呢  先生  有点
But, sir, you do have a meeting with Herds and Gradings. Sir, that's just, oh...
我要死了
Oh, mutton chops.
头羊市长助理  我们需要你的帮助
Assistant Mayor Bellwether, we need your help.
市长助理办公室
Office of the assistant mayor
我们只想看看道路监控录像
we just need to get into the traffic cam database.
毛茸茸的呢
So fluffy!
绵羊从来不让我靠这么近的
Sheep never let me get this close!
你不能随便摸人家的毛
You can't just touch a sheep's wool!
-像棉花糖一样  -住手
- It's like cotton candy. - Stop it!
哪里的
Where to?
雨林区  藤蔓和图洪加街口
Rainforest Dsitrict. Vine and Tujunga.
就是那  全市的道路监控
There. Traffic cams for the whole city.
动物城交通网络
这其实蛮刺激的
This is so exiting actually. I mean, well, you know.
我还从来没干过这么重要的事呢
I never get to do anything this important.
但你可是动物城的市长助理啊
But you're the assistant mayor of Zootopia.
其实就是个名头响亮点的秘书而已
I'm more of a glorified secretary.
我觉得狮心市长只是为了拉来绵羊的选票
I think Mayor Lionheart just wanted the sheep vote.
但他给了我那个漂亮的咖啡杯呢
But he did give me that nice mug.
世界最棒的市长助理(爸爸)
被表扬的感觉还是很好的
Feels good to be appreciated.
臭羊
Smellwether!
就是他给我起的一个有趣外号
That's a fun little name he likes to use.
我叫过他一次狮屁  他一点都不开心
I called him Lionfart once, he did not care for that.
跟你说  那天我可倒了大霉
Let me tell you, it was not a good day for me.
-是  先生  -我不是说要取消下午的事吗
- Yes, sir. - I thought you were gonna cancel my afternoon.
天哪  我得走了  找到什么告诉我
Oh, dear. I better go. Let me know what you find.
真的很感谢你们能
It was really nice for me to be...
韶华易逝  臭羊
While we're young, Smellwether.
你觉得她睡觉的时候会数自己吗
You think when she goes to sleep she counts herself?
闭嘴  好的  道路监控
Shush. Okay, traffic cams..
动物城交通网络
图洪加  图洪加
Tujunga.... Tujunga....
找到了
We're in.
-他们是谁呀  -森林狼
- Who are these guys? - Timberwolves.
瞧瞧这些白痴
Look at these dum-dums.
赌一毛钱他们要嚎叫了
Bet you a nickel one of them's gonna howl.
你看吧
And there it is.
你就说狼为什么非要嚎叫呢
I mean, what is it with wolves and the howling, it's...?
狼嚎  午夜嚎叫
Howlings! Night Howlers!
曼查斯怕的就是这个
That's what Manchas was afraid of,
狼群  午夜嚎叫指的就是狼群
wolves! The wolves are the Night Howlers!
如果曼查斯是他们带走的
If they took Manchas...
带走水獭顿的也是他们
I bet they took Otterton too.
只要找到他们去了哪就可以了
All we gotta do is find out where they went.
冰原镇
热带雨林区
等等  他们去哪了
Wait, where'd they go?
要是我
You know,
干了违法的事要躲监控摄像头
if I wanted to avoid surveillance because I was doing something illegal,
当然我没干过这种事  我会走6B通道
which I never have, I would use the maintenance tunnel 6B.
维修通道
也就是说他们在  这里
Which would put them out... right there.
瞧瞧你  小侦探
Well, look at you, junior detective.
我觉得你当警察肯定很厉害
You know, I think you'd actually make a pretty good cop.
你好大胆子
How dare you.
洋槐小巷  榕树地下通道
Acacia Alley. Ficus Underpass.
南部峡谷
South canyon.
他们是要出城
They're heading out of town.
哪条路通往哪里
Where does that road go?
崖边精神病院
加里  别叫  你要引得大家都叫起来了
Gary, quit it! You're gonna start a howl!
不是我先叫的
I didn't start it.
快走
Come on.
你真是只聪明的小兔子
You are a clever bunny.
看来这儿曾经是所医院
It looks like this was a hospital.
还是你先请  你是警察嘛
You know, after you, you're the cop.
好的  安全
Okay, all clear.
这里的设备都是新的
All this equipment is brand new.
萝卜头
Carrots.
爪痕
Claw marks.
好大好大的爪痕  是什么
Yeah, huge, huge claw marks. What kind of...
曼查斯先生
Mr. Manchas.
是他  找到水獭了
It's him! We found our otter.
水獭顿先生  我是朱迪·霍普斯警官
Mr. Otterton, my name is Officer Judy Hopps.
是你妻子让我来找你的
Your wife sent me to find you.
我们现在就救你出去
We're gonna get you out of here now.
还是别出来了
Or not.
他好像不是很着急回家见老婆
Guess he's in no rush to get home to the missus.
11, 12, 13, 14.
不算曼查斯的话有14个
Not including Manchas, it's... it's fourteen.
牛局长分配了14个失踪动物案件
Chief Bogo handed out 14 missing mammal files.
他们都在这儿
They're all here...
所有失踪动物都在这儿
All the missing mammals are right here.
够了
Enough!
我不要借口  医生  我要的是答案
I don't want excuses, doctor, I want answers.
狮心市长  拜托  我们已经尽力了
Mayor Lionheart, please. We're doing everything we can.
是吗
Really?
因为我面前
Cause I got a dozen and a half animals here
堆着一群疯得没形的动物
who've gone off the rails crazy,
而你连原因都不知道
and you can't tell me why.
我觉得这离尽力还差得远了点
Now I'd call that awfully far from doing everything!
先生  也许该从生物学角度考虑一下了
Sir, it may be time to consider their biology.
什么  什么叫从生物学角度考虑
What? What do you mean "Biology"?
只有食肉动物才会变兽性大发
The only animals going savage are predators.
纸包不住火  我们必须告诉大家
We cannot keep it a secret. We need to come forward.
好主意  告诉民众
Hm, great idea. Tell the public.
你觉得他们会
And how do you think they're
怎么想他们的狮子市长
gonna feel about their mayor who is a lion?!
-我就毁了  -那牛局长怎么说
- I'll be ruined! - Well, what does Chief Bogo say?
牛警长还不知道
Chief Bogo doesn't know.
我们也不会让他知道
And we are going to keep it that way.
爸爸妈妈
糟糕
Oh, no!
-有人在这儿  -先生  你得走了  快
- Someone's here. - Sir, you need to go. Now.
保安  清查本区
Security, sweep the area.
真好  这下死定了
Great, we're dead.
死了  结束  我得死你得死  大家都得死
We're dead. That's it. I'm dead. You're dead. Everybody's dead.
-你会游泳吗  -什么
- Can you swim? - What?
会游泳吗  我会  所以呢
Can I swim? Yes, I can swim. Why?
萝卜头  霍普斯  朱迪
Carrots! Hopps! Judy!
我们得告诉牛局长
We gotta tell Bogo!
您的舞跳的真棒  牛局长
Wow, you are one hot dancer, Chief Bogo.
-牛局长  -我在忙
- Chief Bogo! - Not now.
-等等  是夏奇羚的声音吗  -不是
- Wait, is that Gazelle? - No!
我是夏奇羚  你的舞跳的真棒
I'm Gazelle, and you are one hot dancer.
你也在玩那个应用吗  警长
You have the app too? Chief!
爪豪斯  你没看到
Clawhauser! Can't you see
我正在忙失踪动物案件吗
I'm working on the missing mammal cases?
是的  当然  说到那个案子  长官
Yes, of course. About that, sir.
霍普斯警官来了电话  14个她都找到了
Officer Hopps just called, she found all of them.
好厉害
Wow, I'm impressed.
狮心市长
Mayor Lionheart,
你有权保持沉默  但你所说的一切
you have the right to remain silent. Anything you...
你不理解  我是为了保护这个城市
You don't understand, I was trying to protect the city!
你只想保住你的工作
You were just trying to protect your job.
不  听着  我们还不知道这是怎么回事
No, listen. We still don't know why this is happening.
它会毁了动物城的
It could destroy Zootopia.
你有权保持沉默
You have the right to remain silent.
你说的每一句话
Anything you say can and
都将成为呈堂证供
will be used against you in a court of law.
警察局
雌性雄性们
Ladies and gentlemammals,
失踪的14名动物现已全数找回
14 mammals went missing and all 14 have been found...
找到他们的是下面这位新景观
by our newest recruit, who will speak to you in a moment.
-我好紧张  -媒体见面快速入门
- I'm so nervous. - Okay, press conference 101.
你想表现的聪明点
You wanna look smart,
就要用自己的问题回答他们的问题
answer their question with your own question
然后再回答自己的问题
and then answer that question.
像这样  请问  霍普斯警官
Like this, "Excuse me, Officer Hopps.
这件案子你有什么可以透露的
What can you tell us about the case?"
这案子不简单吗  确实是  懂了吗
"Well, was this a tough case? Yes, yes it was. You see?"
你应该跟我一起上台
You should be up there with me.
这是我们一起完成的
We did this together.
我是个警察吗  不  我不是
Well, am I a cop? No. No, I am not.
真巧你说到这了
Funny you should say that.
因为  我一直在想
Because, well, I've been thinking.
要是有个搭档就好了
It would be nice to have a partner.
给你  如果你需要支笔写字
Here. In case you need something to write with.
霍普斯警官  时间到了
Officer Hopps. It's time.
接下来  有请
So now, I'll turn things over to
解决了本案件的警官
the officer who cracked the case.
朱迪·霍普斯警官
Officer Judy Hopps.
请讲
Yes?
兽性大发的动物您作何评论
What can you tell us about the animals that went savage?
大家都在疑惑的动物
Well, the animals in question.
他们都是不同种类的吗  没错
Are they all different species? Yes. Yes, they are.
好的  那有什么联系呢
Okay, so what is the connection?
我们只知道
All we know is that
他们都是食肉动物
they are all members of the predator family.
所以兽性大发的只有食肉动物吗
So predators are the only ones going savage?
没错  确实如此  没错
That is accu.. Yes, that is accurate, yes.
-为什么  怎么会出现这样的事  -还不知道
- Why? Why is this happening? - We still don't know.
但是
But, emm.
也许和生物学有关
It may have something to do with biology.
您说生物学是什么意思
What do you mean, biology?
就是生物构成
A biological component.
在他们的DNA里
You know, something in their DNA.
他们的DNA  您能详细说一下吗
In their DNA, can you elaborate on that, please?
可以  我是说几千年以前
Yes. What I mean is thousands of years ago
食肉动物捕猎的本能
Eh, predators survived through their...
一直存在着
agressive hunting instincts.
不知为什么
For whatever reason,
他们好像回归了原始  野蛮的本性
they seem to be reverting back to their primitive, savage ways.
霍普斯警官  怎么会出现这样的事呢
Officer Hopps, could it happen again?
这是有可能的  所以我们需要警惕
It is possible. So, we must be vigilant.
警局也做好了万全准备
And we at the ZPD are prepered
我们会保护好大家
and are here to protect you.
会有更多动物兽性大发吗
Will more mammals go savage?
您将采取何种措施保护市民
What is being done to protect us?
您会考虑强制隔离食肉动物吗
Have you considered a mandatory quarantine on predators?
谢谢  霍普斯警官
Okay, thank you, Officer Hopps.
时间到了  请不要再提问了
That's all the time that we have. No more questions.
-我表现如何  -讲得挺好
- Was I okay? - Oh, you did fine.
时间太少了  我还没来得及介绍你
That went so fast, I didn't get a chance to
介绍我们的
mention you or say anything about how we...
你觉得你说的够多了
Oh, I think you said plenty.
什么意思
What do you mean?
显然是他们的生物构成
"Clearly there's a biological component?"
他们好像回归了原始
"These predators may be reverting
野蛮的本性
back to their primitive, savage ways?"
你开玩笑吗
Are you serious?
我只是陈述案件事实
I just stated the facts of the case.
兔子就不可能突然变野蛮
I mean, it's not like a bunny could go savage.
所以狐狸有这种可能
Right, but a fox could? Huh?
尼克  别这样  你跟他们不一样
Nick, stop it, you're not like them.
他们是指谁
Oh, there's a 'them' now?
我意思是  你不是那种食肉动物
You know what I mean, you're not that kind of predator.
要带上口套的那种吗
The kind that needs to be muzzled?
要用防狐喷雾
The kind that makes you think
对付的那种吗
you need to carry around fox repellant?
第一次见面我就发现了
Yeah, don't think I didn't
你带着那瓶小东西
notice that little item the first time we met.
我问你个问题  你害怕我吗
Look. Let me ask you a question. Are you afraid of me?
你觉得我会发疯吗
Do you think I might go nuts?
我会兽性大发吗
You think I might go savage?
我会不会吃了你
You think I might try to eat you?
早料到了
I knew it, huh.
还以为真有人会相信我呢
Just when I thought somebody actually believed in me, huh?
你还是别找食肉动物做搭档了
Probably best if you don't have a predator as a partner.
就职申请
不  尼克  尼克
No, Nick. Nick!
霍普斯警官  那只食肉动物威胁你了吗
Officer Hopps, were you just threatened by that predator?
不  他是我朋友
No, he's my friend.
我们连朋友都不能相信了吗
We can't even trust our own friends?
我没这么说  请让一让
That is not what I said. Please.
-我们安全吗  -有没有狐狸兽性大发了
- Are we safe? - Have any other foxes gone savage?
更多的恶性事件让全市陷入恐慌
More bad news in this city gripped by fear.
最新进展  冰原镇惨剧
一头驯鹿目前生命垂危
A caribou is in critical condition.
起因是遭兽性大发的北极熊袭击
The victim of a mauling by a savage polar bear.
这是继警局的朱迪·霍普斯警官
This, the 27th such attack,
将暴力事件和食肉动物天性关联后
comes just one week after ZPD Officer,
一周以来发生的
Judy Hopps connected the
第27起同类案件
violence to traditionally predatory animals.
与此同时  由巨星夏奇羚
Meanwhile, a peace rally
和平集会现场气氛紧张
组织的和平集会遭到了强烈抵制
organized by popstar Gazelle was marred by protest.
-滚回森林去  食肉动物  -我是大草原来的
- Go back to the forest, predator! - I am from the savannah.
动物城是个独特的地方
Zootopia is a unique place.
夏奇羚呼吁和平
在这个疯狂  美丽  多样化的城市
It's a crazy, beautiful, diverse city.
我们为不同而骄傲
Where we celebrate our differences.
这不是我所熟悉的动物城
This is not the Zootopia I know.
我热爱的动物城不应该是这样
The Zootopia I know is better than this.
大家不会彼此盲目指责
We don't just blindly assign blame.
虽然不知道攻击事件持续发生的原因
We don't know why these attacks keep happening.
但认为所有食肉动物都有兽性是不负责任的
But it's irresponsible to label all predators as savages.
那不是我的艾米特
It's not my Emmitt.
我们不能让恐惧分裂彼此
We cannot let fear divide us.
请把我热爱的动物城还给我
Please give me back the Zootopia I love.
来吧  霍普斯  新市长要见我们
Come on, Hopps. The new mayor wants to see us.
新市长要见我  为什么
The mayor? Why?
你终于功成名就了
It would seem you've arrived.
爪豪斯  你在干嘛
Clawhauser? What are you doing?
他们说  市民来到警察局
They thought it would be better if a predator
一进门就看到像我这只食肉动物
such as myself wasn't the first face that you see
似乎不太好
when you walk into the ZPD.
什么
What?
他们把我调去档案室了  在楼下
They're gonna move me to records. It's downstairs.
锅炉房隔壁
It's by the boiler.
霍普斯
Hopps!
正直  诚实  勇敢
我不太明白
I don't understand.
我们市90%是食草动物  朱迪
Our city is 90 % prey, Judy,
他们现在都吓坏了
and right now they're just really scared.
你是他们的英雄  他们信任你
You're a hero to them. They trust you.
所以我和牛局长
And so that's why Chief Bogo
希望你来当警局的新形象代言人
and I want you to be the public face of the ZPD.
我不是  不是什么英雄
I'm... not... I'm not a hero.
我来到这里是想让世界更美好  但是
I came here to make the world a better place. But...
我搞砸了
...I think I broke it.
别太看得起自己  霍普斯
Don't give yourself so much credit, Hopps.
世界一直都是一团糟  所以才需要好警察
The world has always been broken, that's why we need good cops.
正如你
Like you.
您说的对  长官
With all due respect, sir,
但好警察应该服务于民  保卫家园
a good cop is supposed to serve and protect.
团结人心而不是分裂大家
Help the city. Not tear it apart.
-我配不上警徽  -霍普斯
- I don't deserve this badge. - Hopps.
朱迪  你付出那么多努力来到这里
Judy, you've worked so hard to get here.
这是你从小的梦想
It's what you've wanted since you were a kid.
别放弃啊
You can't quit.
谢谢你们给我的机会
Thank you for the opportunity.
《动物城时报》  局势动荡  城市分裂
一打胡萝卜  谢谢光临
A dozen carrots. Have a nice day.
走吧
Come on.
朱迪  厉害的朱迪
Hey there, Jude. Jude the Dude.
记得这个小名吗  你怎么了
Remember that one? How we doing?
-我很好  -一点都不好  你耷拉着耳朵呢
- I'm fine. - You are not fine, your ears are droopy.
我怎么会妄想自己能改变世界
Why did I think I could make a difference?
因为你敢于尝试
Because you're a trier, that's why.
你从小就爱打破陈规
You've always been a trier.
我的确尝试过了
Oh, I tried.
结果让很多无辜的食肉动物生活更糟糕
And it made life so much worse for so many innocent predators.
也不是全部  说曹操曹操就到  正是时候
not all of them, though. Speak of the devil. Right on time.
吉迪恩·格雷糕点店
那是吉迪恩·格雷吗
Is that Gideon Grey?
没错  就是他  我们一起做生意
Yeah, it sure is. We work with him now.
他是合作伙伴  要不是你让我们放下成见
He's our partner. And we never would have considered it,
-我们也不会和他合作  -说的对
- had you not opened our minds. - That's right.
他现在是三窝区
I mean, kid's turned into one of
最棒的糕点师之一
the top pastry chefs in the tri-burrows.
真是了不起啊
That's... That's really cool, you guys.
吉迪恩·格雷  真没想到
Gideon Grey. I'll be darned.
朱迪
Hey, Judy.
小时候我不懂事
I'd just like to say I'm sorry
我想向你道歉
for the way I behaved in my youth.
因为不自信  为了证明自己厉害
I had a lot of self-doubt, and it manifested itself
才到处惹是生非  欺负弱小
in the form of unchecked rage and agression.
我真是个混蛋
I was a major jerk.
我有时候也有点混蛋
Well, I know a thing or two about being a jerk.
这些派是给你们的
Anyhow, I brought you all these pies.
当心  孩子们  别踩到午夜嚎叫[拉丁文]
Hey, kids! Don't you run through that midnicampum holicithias.
霍普斯先生  那名字太高级了
Well, now. There's a four-dollar word, Mr. H.
我们家的人就叫它午夜嚎叫
My family always just call them Night Howlers.
等等  你刚刚说什么
I'm sorry. What did you say?
他是说那些花儿  朱迪
Kid's talking about those flowers, Judy.
我种了用来驱虫的
I use them to keep the bugs off the produce,
但不能让小家伙们靠近它们
but I don't like the little ones going near them
不然就会像你特里叔叔那样
on acoount of what happened to your uncle Terry.
我们小时候  特里叔叔吃了一整朵
Yeah, Terry ate one whole when we were kids
结果就发疯了
and went completely nuts.
对着你妈妈乱咬一通
He bit the dickens out of your mother.
兔子也会兽性大发
A bunny can go savage.
兽性  那倒不至于
Savage? Well, that's a strong word.
可真是疼死我了
But it did hurt like the devil.
当然疼
sure it did.
你手臂咬了个大洞  要我说就是兽性
There's a sizable divot in your arm. I'd call that savage.
午夜嚎叫不是指狼  是指花儿
Night Howlers aren't wolves, they're flowers.
是花儿让食肉动物兽性大发的
The flowers are making the predators go savage.
原来如此  我知道哪里搞错了
That's it! That's what I've been missing!
钥匙  钥匙  快给我
keys! Keys! Keys! Keys! Hurry, come on!
谢谢  我爱你们  拜拜
Thank you! I love you, bye!
-你听懂她在说啥吗  邦妮  -完全不懂
- You catch any of that, Bon? - Not one bit.
你们也没懂我就放心了
That makes me feel a little bit better,
我以为她在说哪国鸟语呢
I thought she was talking in tongues or something.
谁啊
Who is it?
我得找到尼克  求你了
I need to find Nick. Please.
尼克
Nick?
Nick.
午夜嚎叫不是指狼  是指一种有毒的花
Night Howlers aren't wolves, they're toxic flowers.
我觉得有人故意陷害食肉动物
I think someone is targetting predators on purpose
让他们兽性大发
and making them go savage.
真有意思啊
Isn't that interesting?
等等  请别...我知道你永远不会原谅我了
Wait, please don't.. I know you'll never forgive me.
我能理解
And I don't blame you.
我也不会原谅我自己
I wouldn't forgive me either.
我太无知  又不负责任  还心胸狭窄
It was ignorant, and irresponsible, and small-minded.
但食肉动物不该因为我的过失而受苦
But predators shouldn't suffer because of my mistakes.
我得弥补自己犯的错
I have to fix this.
但是没有你  我办不成
But I can't do it without you.
等我们完成这件事
And... And after we're done...
你怎么恨我
you can hate me. And...
都没关系
And that'll be fine.
因为我是个差劲的朋友  又伤害了你
Because I was a horrible friend and I hurt you.
从一开始你就是对的
And you can walk away knowing that you were right. All along.
我真是只笨兔子
I really am just a dumb bunny.
别担心  萝卜头  我会销毁的  给你48小时
Don't worry, Carrots, I'll let you erase it. In 48 hours.
好了  过来吧
All right, get in here.
你们兔子啊  动不动就哭
Okay. Oh, you bunnies. You're so emotional.
好了  深呼吸
There we go, deep breath.
你该不是要偷这支笔吧
Are you-Are you just trying to steal the pen?
说中了吗
Is that what this is?
-你踩到我尾巴了  快挪开  -对不起
- You are standing on my tail, though. Off, off! - I'm sorry.
霍普斯家族农场
我以为你们只种胡萝卜呢
I thought you guys only grew carrots.
-有什么计划  -我们去追踪午夜嚎叫
- What's your plan? - We are gonna follow the Night Howlers.
行  怎么追
Okay, how?
-认识他吗  -跟你说了  我谁都认识
- Know this guy? - I told you, I know everybody.
走过路过  不要错过
hello! Step right up.
公爵正版影视
应有尽有  只管开口
Anything you need, I got it.
你最爱的电影一应俱全
All your favorite movies.
超能猪战队  长发马公主  无敌破坏犀牛
没上映的都有
I've got movies that haven't even been released yet.
喵阿娜  长颈鹿国历险记  水獭奇缘2
这几部都未上映
八五折  八折
15 % off. 20!
你开价  别走啊
Make me an offer. Come on!
瞧瞧  这是谁啊  盗版公爵
look who it is, the Duke of Bootleg.
你来干嘛  王尔德
What's it to you, Wilde?
不用捣鼓爪子冰棒了吗
Shouldn't you be melting down a Pawpsicle or something?
这不是兔兔警官吗
if it isn't flopsy the copsie.
我们已经知道了  你偷的根本不是洋葱
We both know those weren't only onions I caught you stealing.
你要午夜嚎叫干什么  猥琐屯
What were you gonna do with those Night Howlers, Weselton?
是黄鼠狼  黄鼠狼公爵  我才不告诉你呢  兔子
It's Weaselton, Duke Weaselton. And I ain't talking, rabbit.
你能逼我还是怎么着
And there ain't nothing you can do to make me.
做了他
Ice him.
死耗子  干嘛帮她  她是警察
You dirty rat, why are you helping her? She's a cop!
她还是我未来外孙女的教母
And the godmother to my future granddaughter.
我打算叫她朱迪
I'm gonna name her Judy.
做了这只黄鼠狼
Ice this weasel.
不要  求你了  我什么都说
All right, all right! Please! I'll talk. I'll talk.
我偷午夜嚎叫是要卖掉
I stole the Night Howlers so I could sell them.
他们开的价我实在没法拒绝
They offered me what I couldn't refuse: Money.
你把那些花儿卖给谁了
And to whom did you sell them?
一只叫道格的公羊
A ram named Doug.
我们在地下有个交易点
We got a drop spot underground.
一定要小心  道格绝不是善类
Just watch it. Doug is the opposite of friendly.
榕树街地铁站
他一点都不友好
He's unfriendly.
赶紧地
Come on.
黄鼠狼没有说谎
The weasel wasn't lying.
道格垄断了整个午夜嚎叫的市场
Yeah,it looks like old Doug's cornered the market on Night Howlers.
我是道格  目标是谁
You got Doug here. What's the mark?
撒哈拉广场的猎豹  知道了
Cheetah in Sahara Square. Got it.
什么  我知道他们很快  但我能搞定
Serious? Yeah, I know they're fast, I can hit him.
一只坐在车里的小小水獭
Listen, I hit a tiny little otter
我都能穿过车窗打中
through the open window of a moving car.
搞定了我打你电话
Yeah, I'll buzz you when it's done.
或者你直接看新闻
Or you'll see it on the news.
看那个更快了
You know, whichever comes first.
道格  开门  拿铁来了
Hey, Doug, open up! We've got your latte.
沃尔特和杰西回来了
All right, Woolter and Jesse are back,
我要挂了
so I'm leaving now. Out.
你要去哪里
Hey. Wait, where you going?
你要去哪里  回来
Where are you going? Get back here!
你要干嘛  你会被逮到的
What are you doing? He's gonna see you!
你在看什么
What are you looking at? Hey!
不管你在想什么  别乱来
Whatever you're thinking, stop thinking it.
萝卜头  萝卜头
Carrots. Carrots.
这次让他多加奶泡了吧
You better have the extra foam this time.
开门
Hey! Open up!
你要干嘛  你把我们困在这里了
What are you doing? You just trapped us in here!
我们要把这些证据送到警局
We need to get this evidence to the ZPD.
-装好了  走吧  -要所有的
- Okay, great. Here it is. Got it. - No, all of it.
什么
Wait, what?
你都会开火车了啊
Oh, great, you're a conductor now, huh?
听我说
Hey. Listen.
要启动这堆废铁除非奇迹发生
It would take a miracle to get this rustbucket going.
好吧  哈利路亚
Well. Hallelujah.
实验室这里出了点状况  是大麻烦
We kinda got a situation at the lab. It just got worse!
任务完成
Mission accomplished.
现在嘟嘟鸣笛庆祝会不会有点早
Would it be premature for me to do a little victory toot-toot?
好吧  就嘟一下
All right. One toot-toot.
又一个愿望完成了
Well, I can cross that off the bucket list.
那声鸣笛还是取消吧
I may have to rescind that victory toot-toot.
也许只是下冰雹了
Maybe that's just hail.
走开
Back off!
来了
Incoming!
-萝卜头  -别刹车
- Carrots! - Don't stop! Keep going.
不  快刹车
No, stop. Please stop!
绝对不要刹车
Do not stop this car!
加快速度  尼克
Speed up, Nick. Speed up!
对面有另一辆列车
There's another train coming!
相信我  加速
Trust me, speed up.
停车
Stop the train!
要帮忙吗
Hey. Need some help?
天啊  太快了  抓住
Oh, no. Oh, no no no. Too fast! Too fast! Hold on!
我们该下车了
I think this is our stop.
也许  也许还有证据留下来
Okay, maybe... Maybe some of the evidence survived.
全没了  我们搞砸了
Everything is gone. We've lost it all.
除了这个
Yeah. All, except for this.
太好了  尼克
Nick! Yes!
走吧  我们赶紧送去警局
Come on! We gotta get to the ZPD.
从自然博物馆穿过去
Cut through the Natural History Museum.
-就在那里  -朱迪  朱迪
- There it is. - Judy. Judy!
头羊市长
Mayor Bellwether.
我们知道真相了
We found out what's happening.
有人向肉食动物注射血清
Someone's darting predators with a serum.
所以他们才兽性大发
That's what's making them go savage.
干得真棒 朱迪  我真为你骄傲
I'm so proud of you, Judy. You did just a super job.
谢谢市长
Thank you, ma'am.
你是怎么找到我们的
How did you know where to find us?
我要过去拿箱子了
I'll go ahead and I'll take that case now.
还是我跟尼克送到警局吧
You know what? I think Nick and I will just take this to the ZPD.
-跑  -跑
- Run. - Run.
抓住他们
Get them!
萝卜头
Carrots!
我来扶你  赶紧过来
Here, I got you. Get in here.
先放松下
Okay. Now, just relax.
-吃蓝莓吗  -不用了
- Blueberry? - Pass.
朱迪
Judy.
把箱子拿给牛局长
Take the case. Get it to Bogo.
我不会抛下你的
I'm not gonna leave you behind, that's not happening.
-我走不了  -我们会想到办法的
- I can't walk. - Just.. We'll think of something.
我们都是一样的  朱迪
We're on the same team, Judy.
被人低估  怀才不遇
Underestimated. Underappreciated.
你还没厌倦这一切吗
Aren't you sick of it?
食肉动物就算强壮嗓门大
Predators. They may be strong and loud.
但如果食草动物是食肉动物的十倍
But prey outnumber predators 10 to 1.
试想一下
Think about it.
百分之九十的动物联手对付共同的敌人
90% of the population united against a common enemy.
我们将所向披靡
We'll be unstoppable.
在那里
Over there!
你就该呆在胡萝卜农场里
Well, you should have just stayed on the carrot farm, huh?
太可惜了  我挺喜欢你的
It really is too bad, I did like you.
你想干嘛  杀了我吗
What are you gonna do? Kill me?
当然不是了
No, of course not.
是他
He is.
不  尼克
No! Oh, Nick?
警官  自然历史博物馆里有只兽性大发的狐狸
Yes, police! There's a savage fox in the Natural History Museum!
霍普斯警官已倒下  赶紧过来
Officer Hopps is down. Please hurry!
尼克  你要反抗
No, Nick. Don't do this. Fight it.
但他是无法反抗的
Oh, but he can't help it. Can he?
食肉动物的天生就有兽性
Since predators are just biologically predisposed to be savages.
想想明天的头条
Gosh! Think of the headline!
英雄警官被兽性狐狸所杀害
Hero Cop Killed by Savage Fox.
你的目的就是这个吗
So that's it?
食草动物畏惧食肉动物然后你掌权
Prey fears predator, and you stay in power?
差不多吧
Yeah. Pretty much.
不会得逞的
It won't work.
畏惧总能管用的
Fear always works.
为了这目的  我会给所有肉食动物都打一针
And I'll dart every predator in Zootopia to keep it that way.
尼克  不
Oh, Nick. No.
再见了  小兔子
Bye-bye, bunny.
流血  血  血  和死亡
Blood, blood, blood! And death.
好了好了  强行抢戏吗
All right, you know you're milking it.
而且  我觉得我们成功了
Besides, I think we got it. I think we got it.
我们成功了  谢谢你  叨叨羊
We got it up there, thank you, yakety-yak.
你全盘招认了
You laid it all out beautifully.
什么
What?
你是在找血清吗
Yeah. Oh, are... are you looking for the serum?
在这呢
Well, it's right here.
你武器里的
What you've got in the weapon there,
是我家里农场种的蓝莓
those are blueberries, from my family's farm.
可好吃了  你该尝尝
They are delicious. You should try some.
我陷害了狮心  我也可以陷害你
I framed Lionheart, I can frame you too.
你们空口无凭
It's my word against yours.
其实呢
Actually...
我会给所有肉食动物都打一针
And I'll dart every predator in Zootopia to keep it that way.
我都录下来了
It's your word against yours.
这叫智取  亲爱的
It's called a hustle, Sweetheart. Boom!
前任市长晨曦·头羊已入狱
Former mayor, Dawn Bellwether is behind bars today,
前市长头羊入狱
罪名是策划了动物城
guilty of masterminding the savage attacks
食肉动物野蛮袭击事件
that have plagued Zootopia of late.
她的前任上司  里奥多·狮心
Her predecessor, Leodore Lionheart,
狮心终于发声
否认所有与其密谋的指控
denies any knowledge of her plot,
声称只是为了保护动物城
claiming he was just trying to protect the city.
我囚禁这些动物是错的吗
Did I falsely imprison those animals?
是的  我确实错了
Well, yes. Yes, I did.
这是经典的
It was a classic
为了正确的目的做了错事
doing the wrong thing for the right reason kind of a deal.
另外  医生宣称
In related news, doctors say
午夜嚎叫解药已见成效
午夜嚎叫的解药
the Night Howlers' antidote is proving effective
已让受害食肉动物逐渐恢复
in rehabilitating the afflicted predators.
艾米特
Oh, Emmitt!
谢谢
Thank you.
我小时候
When I was a kid,
我以为动物城是完美的地方
I thought Zootopia was this perfect place.
人人和谐相处
Where everyone got along,
谁都能成就无限可能
and anyone could be anything.
现在发现
Turns out,
现实远比宣传口号
real life is a little bit more complicated
要复杂
than a slogan on a bumper sticker.
现实生活是糟糕的
Real life is messy.
我们都有局限性
We all have limitations.
都会犯错
We all make mistakes.
但是乐观点来说  我们也都很像
Which means, hey, glass half full, we all have a lot in common.
我们越是努力了解别人
And the more we try to understand one another.
越会变得出色
The more exceptional each of us will be.
但凡事都要去尝试
But we have to try.
不管你是什么类型的动物
So no matter what type of animal you are.
从巨大的大象到第一只狐狸警官
From the biggest elephant, to our first fox.
我恳请你们
I implore you.
努力尝试  让世界变得更美好
Try... Try to make the world a better place.
尼古拉斯·P·王尔德警官
审视自己的内心  从改变自己开始
Look inside yourself and recognize that change starts with you.
从我做起  从我们做起
It starts with me. It starts with all of us.
动物城警察学校
好了好了  安静
All right, all right, enough. Shut it!
今早我们来了几位新人
We have some new recruits with us this morning.
包括第一只狐狸警官
Including our first fox.
谁在乎呢
Who cares.
你的话应该印到鸡汤卡片上  长官
You should have your own line of inspirational greeting cards, sir.
闭嘴  王尔德
Shut your mouth, Wilde.
任务分配
Assignments.
灰熊利  牙迈尔  德尔加多警官  冰原镇反恐特警组
Officers Grizzoli, Fragmeyer, Delgato. Tundratown SWAT.
吼洛夫  河马金斯和狼法德  卧底
Snarlov, Higgins, Wolfard. Undercover.
霍普斯和王尔德  交通巡逻
Hopps, Wilde. Parking duty.
解散
Dismissed.
开玩笑的
Just kidding!
接到投诉  萨凡纳中心有人飙车
We have reports of a street racer tearing up Savannah Central.
找到他  把他缉捕归案
Find him. Shut him down.
兔子开车都那么烂吗  还是只是你
So are all the rabbits bad drivers, or is it just you?
抱歉
Oops. Sorry.
狡猾的兔子
Sly bunny.
蠢狐狸
Dumb fox.
你知道你爱我
You know you love me.
真的吗
Do I know that?
是的  是真的
Yes. Yes, I do.
天生慢
先生  你时速已飙到115英里
Sir, you were going 115 miles per hour,
我希望你能给我个合理的解释
I hope you have a good explanation.
闪电  闪电  数你最快
Flash, Flash. Hundred Yard Dash!
尼克
Nick...
晚上好  动物城
Good evening, Zootopia!
各位  举起你们的双爪
Come on, everybody. Put your paws up.
I messed up tonight, I lost another fight *
I still mess up but I'll just start again *
I keep falling down, I keep on hitting the ground *
I always get up now to see what's next *
I won't give up, no I won't give in *
'Til I reach the end and then I'll start again *
No I won't leave, I wanna try everything *
I wanna try even though I could fail *
I won't give up, no I won't give in *
'Til I reach the end and then I'll start again *
No, I won't leave, I wanna try everything *
I wanna try even though I could fail *
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh *
Try everything *
举起你们的双爪
Put your paws in the air, come on.
* Look how far you've come, you filled your heart with love *
* Baby you've done enough, take a deep breath *
* Don't beat yourself up, don't need to run so fast *
* Sometimes we come last, but we did our best *
* I won't give up, no I won't give in *
* 'Til I reach the end and then I'll start again *
* No I won't leave, I wanna try everything *
* I wanna try even though I could fail *
* I won't give up, no I won't give in *
* 'Til I reach the end and then I'll start again *
* No I won't leave, I wanna try everything *
* I wanna try even though I could fail *
* I'll keep on making those new mistakes *
* I'll keep on making them every day *
* Those new mistakes *
* Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh *
* Try everything *
大家一起
Come on!
大家一起摇起尾巴
Shake your tail with me come on
* I'll keep on making those new mistakes *
* I'll keep on making them every day *
* Those new mistakes *
* Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh *
* Try everything *